▍2026 美网 男单1/4决赛
哈恰诺夫 6-2 7-5 3-2 布洛克斯 · 赛后场上采访
Karen, congratulations.
卡伦 恭喜你
I know it's maybe not the way you
我知道 这可能不是你
wanted it to end, but let's talk
想要的结束方式 不过我们聊聊
about your form coming into here.
你来这儿时的状态
Where where did all this confidence come
这一身自信
from?
到底是哪来的？
It's been a new Karen Khachanov.
像是换了一个哈恰诺夫
I mean, it's not new.
其实不新
I would say it's old in a way.
某种程度上还是老样子
Yeah, look, Alex,
是这样 Alex
I was preparing really really well
我准备得非常非常充分
for for that matchup.
为了这场对阵
It's not easy really to play
这场球其实不好打
because from one side I was feeling I was
因为一方面 我感觉自己
dominating from the beginning.
从一开始就占着上风
Then I started to feel like he was struggling
后来我开始感觉到
more and more.
他越来越吃力
And and you know it's a mixed feeling
那种感觉很复杂
because I feel like I'm better let's say
因为可以说 我更占便宜
in certain situations he's suffering.
而某些时候他在难受
I don't want to scream come
我不想去喊加油
on or something like
或者类似的话
that you know and and I wanted
而且我想
to keep the energy still there
把力气留着
but yeah look I wish him
但不管怎么说
a speedy recovery.
我祝他早日康复
Definitely I saw
我确实看得很清楚
that really he was suffering all over his body
他浑身都在难受
and I'm super happy guys.
而我特别开心
I'm in semi-finals.
我进四强了
Come on.
太棒了
Yeah that's right.
是的 没错
Semi-finals. Congratulations.
半决赛 恭喜你
Second time now in the semi-finals here.
这是你第二次在这儿打进四强
What do you feel like you learned
你觉得从第一次
from the first time and ready
学到了什么
to take another step forward?
准备好再往前一步了吗？
Yeah, look we'll see.
是啊 走着看吧
We'll see. Obviously obviously it's a goal,
走着看 这当然是个目标
you know, once you are in the semi-finals,
一旦进了四强
you are thinking
你自然会想着
to make one more step forward.
再往前迈一步
You know,
你知道
I will definitely now watch Sasha
我肯定会看兹维列夫
against Botic
对范德赞德舒尔普那场
and prepare whoever wins
谁赢了就准备谁
and try to do my best as always, you know.
一如既往 尽我所能
Well, I always see you doing your best.
我每次看你都是全力以赴
I always see you physically ready.
身体状态一直很好
It seems like the three out
看起来五盘三胜这个赛制
of five format is is great for you.
特别适合你
What kind of training do you do to be I
你平时都怎么训练
don't think I've ever seen you tired out here.
我好像没见你在这儿累过
Yeah, I was thinking even maybe
是啊 我刚还在想
to go to serve now a little bit, you know,
现在就去练会儿发球
because the percentage was not so high.
因为成功率不太高
At the same time, I have tomorrow day off.
同时 我明天休息一天
I mean, recovery day and practice day.
也就是恢复加训练的一天
So, definitely I don't like
说实话 我不喜欢
to to have a days off.
有休息日
You know, once you're in this rhythm,
一旦进了这个节奏
in this dynamics, in this momentum,
进了这种势头里
you want to keep going unless it
就想一直打下去
was a really, really difficult match
除非那场球实在太苦
that you say, "Okay,
苦到你会说 好吧
I cannot I cannot stand up," you know.
我都站不起来了
Well, congratulations,
那么 恭喜你
semi-finalist Karen Khachanov.
打进四强的哈恰诺夫
Thank you, guys. Thank you.
谢谢大家 谢谢